Ding ding pch n daa, bam-ba-ba-re-bam
baram bom bom baba-bam-bam-bommm
Wh-wha-what's going on-on?
ding ding
This is the Crazy Frog!
bem bem
ring ding d-d ding ding
ring ding d-d bem bem bem
ring ding d-d boa boa
ring ding d-d ding ding
ring ding d-d bem bem bem
This is the Crazy Frog
break down
ding ding
Br-br-break it, br-break it
dum dum dubdara dub da dum dum
dubdada dum dum dubdada da bamm
bem bem
dum dum dubdada dub da dum dum
dubdada dum dum d-d-da dum
Dum dum dumda dum dum dum
This is the Crazy Frog
ram me am brem da
m da rem ram am da baabeeeaaaaaaa!
ding ding
This is the Crazy Frog
dahhh da
ring ding ding ding ding ding
ring ding ding ding bem bem bem
ring ding ding ding baa baa
ring ding ding ding ding ding
ring ding ding ding bem bem bem
This is the Crazy Frog
ding ding
Br-br-break it, br-break it
dum dum dumda dum dum dum
bem bem
This is the Crazy Frog
bem bem!